

+263 77 212 8622

doug.maposa@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/douglasmaposa

ttps://www.twitter.com/code\_writer

🕝 https://www.github.com/the-code-writer

ttps://www.douglas-maposa.site

## ABOUT ME

As a full-stack engineer with over 10 years of experience, I have mastered the art and science of creating engaging and intelligent digital solutions. From prototyping to UI/UX design, frontend development, backend development, devops, machine learning and artificial intelligence.

I have the necessary skills and knowledge to handle technical challenges. I use agile, scrum, kanban, design thinking and emotional intelligence to manage projects and teams effectively and efficiently, ensuring a smooth and successful software development life cycle.

My dream is to create a more open and connected world, where sovereign people can collaborate, socialize, learn and work using the power and potential of Web3.0. I am always eager to explore new and emerging trends in the distributed space as I am passionate about all things blockchain.

I have a Bachelor of Science Honors degree in Information Technology and am currently studying a Master of Science in Computer Science with Colorado Boulder State University. I am committed to continuous learning and growth as an engineer, mentor and a team leader.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**FULLSTACK ENGINEER Dovellous Technologies** Fully Remote

**WEB 3.0 DEVELOPER - CONTRACT** 

Swapps Finance **Fully Remote** 

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Inbox Group Al Harare, Zimbabwe (Hybrid)

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER AppDev (Pvt) Ltd Harare, Zimbabwe (Onsite)

**GRAPHIC & WEB DEVELOPER** Pixelus Design Lab (Pvt) Ltd Harare, Zimbabwe (Onsite)

NOV 2021 - Present

OCT 2021 - DEC 2021

JUL 2018 - SEP 2021

JAN 2013 - JUL 2018

**AUG 2012 - DEC 2012** 

#### **EDUCATION**

BSC HONORS IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Midlands State University Gweru, Zimbabwe

**AUG 2008 - JUN 2012** 

ADVANCED DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY Satra Learning Centre Harare, Zimbabwe

AUG 2005 - SEP 2007

# PROFESSIONAL COURSES

- Blockchain Specialization
- Machine Learning
- IBM Fullstack Engineer
- Meta Frontend Developer
- Meta Backend Developer
- Meta Database Engineer
- Software Design & Architecture
- **UIUX Specialization**
- Terraform DevOps Masterclass
- Ethereum & Solidity Masterclass
- DEFI: Primitives & Deep Dive
- NFT Development
- **Amazon Web Services**
- Cyber Security

### **SKILLS**

- NextJS, ReactJS, Redux, Typescript
- HTML5, Tailwind CSS, Javascript
- UIUX, Figma, Adobe XD, CorelDraw
- Solidity, Hardhat, Ethers, Wagmi, Viem
- IPFS, S3, AWS, GCP, NFT, ERC, ZK
- MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Node JS
- Python, Go Lang, Rust, PHP, Express JS
- GraphQL, Restful APIs, Serverless
- Ethereum, Polygon, Solana Blockchains
- Git, CI/CD Pipelines, Microservices



























